## Yusuf Saleh

## Front End Developer & UI/UX Designer

-----

Address: Sadat City & Shebin El-kom WhatsApp: 01005563956
Email: ucef.sale7@gmail.com

**LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/yusuf-sale7

Website: yusuf-saleh.me

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Meticulous web developer and UI/UX with over 3 years of front-end experience & 2 years of UI/UX and passion for responsive web design and modern mobile app design. Hoping to share my skills, expertise and experience with a progressive and forward-thinking company to increase and enhance my experience.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

**Front End Developer & UI/UX Designer** 03/2019 – Present Takkat Solutions., Menouf

#### Responsibilities:

- Knowledge into design and creation of effectual user interfaces.
- Translate UI designs into high quality web design.
- Capability and willingness to study new software applications.
- Knowledge of current web design techniques and trends.
- Code source tools (Git, TFS).
- Create a single page web app.
- Implements user-centered/ focused designs and processes in order to identify specific user needs and find best solutions.
- Translate websites and app documentation into a high quality UI designs.

Collaborates closely with the app development team to bring prototypes into the production code process.

**Front End Developer & UI/UX Designer** 06/2018 – 03/2019 NTS Co., The 5<sup>th</sup> Settlement

### Responsibilities:

- Knowledge into design and creation of effectual user interfaces.
- Translate UI designs into high quality web design.
- Capability and willingness to study new software applications.

- Knowledge of current web design techniques and trends.
- Implements user-centered/ focused designs and processes in order to identify specific user needs and find best solutions.
- Translate websites and app documentation into a high quality UI designs.
- Collaborates closely with the app development team to bring prototypes into the production code process.

## **Front End Developer**

03/2017 - 05/2018

Creadev, Shebin Elkom

## Responsibilities:

- Knowledge into design and creation of effectual user interfaces.
- Translate UI designs into high quality web design.
- Capability and willingness to study new software applications.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.

#### **EDUCATION**

2015 - Present

**Bachelor Degree of Computer Science**, Menoufia University

### Additional SKILLS

**Technical**: HTML, CSS, Javascript, UIKIT, jQuery, Bootstrap, Vue JS, C#, Java, Kotlin.

**Adobe products**: Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Lightroom.

**Microsoft products**: Github, Visual studio, VS Code, TFS, Office.

Other: Atom (Code editor), Brackets (Code editor).

## Accomplishments

You can check all works from here: <a href="https://yusuf-saleh.me">https://yusuf-saleh.me</a>

**Note:** Some websites and dashboards are private or not published yet.